elizabethannedesigns.com 2014-11-13

# Our Policies - Elizabeth Anne Designs: The Wedding Blog

Your use of this site and its services is governed by these policies, as well as our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.elizabethannedesigns.com/blog/terms/). Please read them carefully. By accessing or using the site and its services you agree to be bound by these policies and Terms and Conditions, whether or not you are a registered user (“user(s)”) of the services. If you do not agree to these policies and Terms and Conditions, you are not authorized to use the site or its services.

### Editorial Policy (Including Social Media)

EAD is lovingly curated by founder/editor Ami Price (hi!), and the [EAD team](http://www.elizabethannedesigns.com/blog/about). I publish what I love, and hope that you love it too!

In addition to editing and reviewing all editorial content, I also personally screen applications for each sponsor we accept. The integrity of the EAD brand is far more important to me than money, so know that I only accept sponsorship requests from companies that I truly believe are right for the site and for all of you lovely readers. With that in mind, please know that we do publish sponsored posts on the site, which are clearly noted, and we also do promote brands and products that we adore.

To be clear, any time EAD accepts money for promoting a product or vendor, we will disclose it. There are also times where we link to products (either on the site on via our social media accounts), and if you decide to purchase the product or other products on that site, we receive a commission. If you don’t purchase anything, or if you purchase something and return it, we don’t receive any compensation. Currently, we partner with the service rewardStyle to promote products we love from awesome companies such as Modcloth, Shopbop, Crane & Co. and more. If you see a link that says “rstyle.me”, that’s a link where we receive commissions if you purchase something from the site. If you have any questions about this, feel free to [email me](mailto:ami@elizabethannedesigns.com)!

All sponsored posts are clearly noted within the blog post, which one of the EAD team members has personally written. At times, work from the Elizabeth Anne Designs sponsors will be featured in real weddings and other features; however, unless specifically disclosed as a sponsored post, these features and links are solely based upon the quality of the work and are not paid editorial content. Sponsorship does not in any way guarantee editorial coverage, and sponsors do not receive any preference with regard to editorial consideration.

Advertisements on the site are clearly noted as “sponsors”, “vendor guide members”, or “featured vendors”. For more information about advertising on EAD, please visit our [sponsorship information page](http://www.elizabethannedesigns.com/blog/advertising-on-ead). More information about the Vendor Guide is available [here](http://www.elizabethannedesigns.com/blog/vendor-guide/about/).

All of the content on EAD is published with the best information we have at the time of publication. However, product offerings, websites, and businesses do change, so we cannot guarantee that all archived links and content remain accurate as of the time of reading.

If you have an item you’d like to submit for feature on EAD, find out how to do so using our [submissions page](http://www.elizabethannedesigns.com/blog/submissions).

### Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@elizabethannedesigns.com.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy document outlines how personal information is received, collected, and used.

_Third Party ad servers and networks_

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to deliver advertisements that appear on Elizabeth Anne Designs. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Elizabeth Anne Designs. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to EAD and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy here: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

Cox Digital Solutions, as a third party vendor, may utilize techonology to collect anonymous information about your visit to Elizabeth Anne Designs, including information about the ads displayed, cookies placed, and your IP address. To opt out of information collection by Cox Digital Solutions or view their privacy policy, visit <http://www.coxdigitalsolutions.com/privacy-policy/consumer-opt-out-program>.

Burst Media, as a third party vendor, may use cookies to improve your Web browsing experience. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer for the purpose of identifying your web browser. When you are served a Burst ad, Burst may assign in a cookie various information on ads you’ve seen, information on sites you’ve visited and activities performed to your computer browser. In an effort to respect your privacy, Burst Media gives all internet users the choice to opt-out of receiving Burst Media cookies. If you would like to opt out, please visit our Cookie Opt-out Program at [www.burstmedia.com/optout.html](http://www.burstmedia.com/optout.html).

_Information Gathering and use of Personal Information_

Elizabeth Anne Designs collects certain data for all site visitors including IP addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider, date and time of visit, page views, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. Name and email address are required to post a comment on Elizabeth Anne Designs. Your email address and other identifiable personal information is never shared, unless required by law.

_Consent_

By accessing EAD and providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of this information in accordance with this policy.
